# **Cory Cross**

Solution-driven professional excelling in highly collaborative, as well as individual work environments. Well versed in communication with clients as well as team members. Proven experience developing consumer-focused web sites using HTML, CSS, PHP, JavaScript as well as other languages and frameworks. A willingness to learn and apply new tools when necessary. Open and Experience building products for desktop and mobile users, meeting highest standards for web design, user experience, best practices, usability and speed. Responding to challenges by designing and developing solutions and building web applications aligned to customer's specifications. Educated in Object-Oriented and procedural programing using C++,C, and Java.

### **Work History**

Current

## 2015-04 - Web Developer

Beanstalk Web Solutions, Webster Groves, Missouri

- Communicate with clients to get specifications for web based projects
- Developed custom websites using CMS platforms such as Wordpress, Magento, October, Drupal.
- Use languages such as HTML, CSS, PHP, Javascript, to develop websites, and web applications.
- Maintained hosting environment for 200+ websites
- Train and troubleshoot clients on usage of web based programs.

## 2012-04 - Sales Associate 2015-09

Guitar Center, Bridgeton, MO

- Commission based sales of musical equipment
- Maintenance of inventory and upkeep of retail store

#### Education

2015-12

## 2010-09 - Bachelor of Science: Computer Science

University of Missouri St.Louis - St. Louis, MO

• Minored in Mathmatics

#### **Personal Info**

#### **Address**

1457 De Porres Ln St.Charles, MO, 63304

#### **Phone**

636 699 2811

#### E-mail

corycross14@gmail.com

#### **Skills**

HTML

**CSS** 

PHP

Javascript

Wordpress

Magento

SQL

Java

C

C++